previously on...
前情回顾
you're awfully brave buyinga place site unseen.
还没看房就买下了你们胆子真大
We could tell from the advertisement it was just what we were looking for.
- 我们看广告就知道这桩肯定没错的
Sometimes...
（有些时候）
who ever said you were the father?
谁说我怀的孩子是你的了
Didn't you thinkit was strange that you have the only lawn on wisteria lane
你难道就从来不觉得奇怪 Wisteria Lane上只有你家的草坪 需要每周修建三次
that needed to be mowedthree times a week?
Wisteria Lane上只有你家的草坪 需要每周修建三次
I am going to kill you!
我要宰了你
The truth about our loved ones...
（我们深爱的人的真相）
you asked peterson's wife tomake sure he wouldn't promote me
是你跟Peterson的老婆说不给我升职的
so I quit. I'm gonna bea stay-at-home dad.
我不干了 我在家当全职父亲
We should... talk about this.
我们得好好谈谈
You're goin' back to work.
你回你的职场吧
Can lead you into harm's way.
(会给你带来伤害）
I think I'm havinga heart attack.
我心脏病犯了
You are gonna come throughthis operation just fine.
你的手术会很顺利的
Hello?
你好
rex passed awayabout ten minutes ago.
Rex十分钟前过世了
I'm so sorry.
我很遗憾
Mr. Delfino took my dad awayto kill him.
Delfino要杀了我爸爸
Now I'm gonna killmr. Delfino.
现在我要杀了Delfino
It was an accepted fact among the residents of wisteria lane
（Wisteria Lane上人人都知道）
that ida greenberg liked her liquor.
（Ida  Greenburge爱酒成性）
People had seen her drunk at sewing bees...
（针织会的时候她是醉得）
the department of motor vehicles...
(交管署门前她是醉得)
and the first methodist church.
（甚至第一次去美以美教堂的时候也是醉得） ((一种教派))
Ida had tried to quit drinking many times,
（Ida曾多次想要戒酒）
but she couldn'T.
（但她做不到）
Then one night in a moment of despair,
（就在这天晚上）
she challenged god
（绝望的她望天挑战上帝）
to quench her never-ending thirst.
（让他遏止她对酒精的渴望）
Luckily for ida,god was listening.
（Ida真是幸运） （上帝听到了她的祈求）
zach,listen to me.
Zach 你听我说
No!
不要
Not so tough now,are you?
现在看你还怎么逞能
Uh! Ow! Oh! Bongo,no!
Bango 别
Bongo!Bongo!
Bango
It was at that moment it occurred to ida
（就在那一刻 Ida终于认识到）
god may work in mysterious ways,
（上帝行事可以很神秘）
but he isn't particularly subtle.
（但也可以非常直接）
Sync:YTET-fisherchen -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 七宝 校对: 七宝 时间轴: fisherchen [Desperate Housewives]-[欲乱绝情妻] 第二季 第一集
Desperate Housewives
[Desperate Housewives]-[欲乱绝情妻] 第二季 第一集
It had been a year since my death,
（我已经过世1年之久了）
and a lot had changed on wisteria lane.
（Wisteria Lane上发生了很多改变）
children had learned new games.
（孩子玩玩起了新的游戏）
New neighbors had moved in.
（社区搬来了新的邻居）
Old houses had been rebuilt...
（老房子换上了新装）
And fresh tragedies had occurred.
（而悲剧也上演了新的一辄）
In one house,
（在一栋房子里) ( 一位寡妇准备通知她的朋友丈夫的死讯）
a widow was getting ready to tell her friends of her husband's passing.
But until the time was right,
(但没到时候她不打算拨通电话）
she would wait.
And life,as it tends to do,
（好像这样 生活才能照常进行)
would go on.
I look like hell. I need a hairbrush.
来人了 我得梳梳头
Yeah,um,ahem,that's not gonna help.
是啊 不过你问题不在头发
Susan,
Susan 警官来要你的口供
officer romslove is here for your statement.
Zach young do that?
这是Zach Young干的么
No. She fell. Bit her lip. It was an accident.
不是 她摔倒了
Okay.
咬到了嘴唇 是个意外
So,uh,walk me through what happened.
好吧 那你告诉我事情的经过吧
well,I went over to mike's to feed the dog.
不知道 哦当时在喂狗
- I'm sorry?
- 什么？
Feed the dog.
在喂狗
and I turned around,
我转过身 Zach Young就在我身后
and there was zach young--
and that's zach with an "h"--
你落了个h
- pointing a gun at me.
- 他拿枪指着我
The doctor said keep that in.
医生不让你把它拿出来
You gotta understand,zach's had a tough time.
希望你能明白 Zach过的很不容易
- He's got emotional issues--
- 他有情绪问题
'cause he's crazy.
搭戏个疯西（他是个疯子）
Still,I don't think he meant to hurt anybody.
但他没想伤害任何人
Uh,hello! Uh,he was waiting there for you to come home
什么 他在那等你回来好杀了你
so he could kill you.
Is that what happened when you got home?
你回家后他有要杀你么 对你开枪？
The kid took a shot at you?
Actually,susan fired the gun.
事实是Susan开的枪
That's because I was wrestling it away from zach
那是因为我在和Zach争抢 以防他对你开枪
so that he wouldn't shoot you.
Oh,there's blood.
哦 血
Could we do this later? She's kind of a mess right now.
咱们稍后再录口供好么 她现在已经一团糟了
Yeah,I think I can fill in the rest for you.
我想我能替她讲讲
I'd appreciate it.
再好不过了
- You feel better,mrs. Mayer.
- 祝你早日康复 Mayer女士
Thanks.
再见
Ow! That hurts.
啊 好疼
- I'm gonna get you more ice.
- 我给你取点冰
Okay.
好的
No,I'm tellin' you.
Susan埋怨那孩子是有点过于激动了
Susan really flew off the handle when she jumped the kid.
So you're saying this was more of a domestic squabble?
那么你的意思整个事件只是一次口角了
Definitely,yeah.
没错 是的
Are we required to press charges?
我们必须要提出诉讼么
Well,you're not really required,
并不是“必须”
but it's something you should really consider when a handgun is involved.
但有枪支卷入进来你应该好好考虑一下
John!
- How did you get in here?
- 你怎么进来的
I know where you keep the key.
我知道备用钥匙在哪
- Mimosa?
- 喝点么
No,I'm pregnant,you jackass.
我有孕在身 白痴
I made yours with seltzer.
我用碳酸水冲得
Do you have any idea what you've done?
你知道你干了些什么么
That little stunt you pulled yesterday in the courtroom
你昨天在法庭的那场戏 能让carlos做上8年的牢
could get carlos sent away for eight years.
Yeah,I thought you might be a little mad about that.
是啊 我知道你会生我气
But once you calm down,
但你冷静下来想一想
you'll see that it's just the two of us.
现在就剩我们俩了 这多好啊
It's gonna be awesome.
you brought luggage?
你把行李都带来了？
He's gone. We don't have to sneak around anymore.
他进监狱了 我们不用躲躲藏藏了
We can have a real relationship.
我们能正常的交往了
It's what's best for the three of us.
这对我们三个人都好
The three of us? How exactly does that benefit carlos?
三个人？ carlos得到什么好处了？
- I'm talking about my baby.
- 我是说我的孩子
You don't know it's your baby.
你怎么知道这是你的孩子
I don't even know it's your baby.
连我都不知道
And I don't wanna know 'cause it doesn't matter.
我也不想知道 因为这无关紧要
so what,you don't love me?
那你什么意思 你不爱我么
Well,up until the point that you told my husband we were having an affair,
在你告诉我丈夫 我们偷情之前我还挺喜欢你的
I was quite fond of you.
Since then...
从那以后
not a fan!
没那么着迷了
Oh,why on earth would you let them finger paint before breakfast?
嗨 哦 还没吃早饭干吗让他们做手指画
It's my job to clean that up now,so it's my call,right?
现在我负责打扫 所以我说了算 是吧？
You're right. I'm sorry.
你说得对 对不起
Hey,I thought the meeting wasn't until 1.
哎 我以为1点才开会呢
Oh,I have a thousand things to do before that--
在那之前我有好多事要做呢
borrow a decent scarf from bree,
管Bree借条像样的围巾
buy a lipstick I don't hate--
买个适合我的唇膏
- mommy,mommy,look!
- 妈妈 妈妈 看
Aah! No! No!
阿 别 别 别
No,nobody touches mommy,okay?
谁也别碰妈妈 好么？
I love you,I love your finger painting,
我爱你 我爱你的手指画
but if you touch me with those messy hands,
但你要是用你那小脏手碰我
I will cut them off.
我就把它们剁下来
Go on. Off. Good.
去 一边玩去
It's okay.
没事的
- A little nervous?
- 有点紧张？
Who,me?
谁？我？
I've been out of work for seven years,
我7年都没工作了
I'm a woman of a certain age in a business that values youth above all else.
我都是中年妇女了 而却要在一个青春比什么都值钱的行业里工作
- Why should I be nervous?
- 你说我有什么可紧张的
You are experienced.
你有经验
You are brilliant.
你很精明
You are going to nail this job interview,okay?
你肯定能搞定这份工作的 好啦
Thank you.Uh,no. I can'T...
谢谢 阿 别 我不能...
you're very... so...
你有点... 所以...
Thank you. Here.
好吧 谢谢
Oh,my cell phone.
来 哦 我的手机
lynette,hi,it's bree.
Lynett 嗨 是我Bree
I do hope I'm not calling too early.
希望我没有打得太早 嗯？
Hmm?
Oh,of course you can borrowthat scarf.
哦 你当然可以借那条围巾
I'll press it for you.
我一会帮你熨熨
Um,I have,uh,some news.
唔 我 有事要告诉你 Rex过世了
Rex died.
I thought they weregonna operate. What happened?
他们不是要进行手术么？怎么了
Apparently rex's heartjust gave out.
似乎Rex的心脏停跳了
Oh,my god.
哦 天哪 我们什么时候能看到Bree
So when can we see bree?
She saidshe was gonna call.
她说她会来电话的
She's gota lot of things to do,
她很忙 要筹备葬礼什么的
planning for the funeral,that sort of thing.
She doesn't lookthat busy to me.
我看她似乎不怎么忙啊
Hi,hi. What are youdoing out here?
嗨 你在这干什么呢
Oh,I'm just waitingfor,uh,rex's mother.
我在等Rex的母亲 她马上就到了
She's gonna be hereany second.
Honey,we are so sorry.
亲爱的 我们很难过
Oh,do one of youdrink soy milk?
哦 你们有人要喝豆奶么
I was cleaning outthe fridge this morning,
早上我清理冰箱时候发现的
and rex is the only onewho drinks it.
家里除了Rex没人喝
I just bought it on friday.I'd hate to throw it away.
我周五才买的 我不想扔了
What a waste.
可惜了
Oh,sweetie.
哦 宝贝儿
Honey,you can let it out.
亲爱的 你别这么撑着
No. No,I can't affordto fall apart right now.
不 不 我现在不能垮掉
Why?
为什么
You're about to find out.
你们这就知道了
bree!
Bree！
Oh,stop here.This is the house.
停车 就是这栋房子
Is that...
这是...
yes,that is rex's mother.
对 这是Rex的母亲
I can't believe it.
太难以相信了
It's likesome hideous nightmare.
简直是场恶梦
My life is over!
我没法活了
没法活了
it appears there's a 7-year gapsince your last position.
看来你上次工作已经是7年前了
What,did you takesome time off?
怎么了 想休息一阵？
I was a stay-at-home mom.
我在家带孩子 我倒希望是休息
I wish it had been time off.
- Boy or girl?
- 男孩还是女孩？
A girl...
女孩
- and three boys.
- 还有3个男孩
Four kids?
4个孩子？
Yeah,of course,they won'tget in the way of the job
是啊 当然他们不会妨碍我完成工作
because my husband's stayinghome with them from now on.
因为从现在开始我丈夫在家带孩子
I knew I could never doboth jobs justice.
我知道我不可能家里家外的忙
That's why I chosenot to have a family.
所以我决定一个人过
I didn't want to be oneof those kind of women--
我不想成为那种女人--- 因为要带孩子看医生
you know,sloughingthings off onto coworkers
because ofa pediatrician appointment or a dance recital.
或参加孩子的演出 把工作推给同事
I get really neuroticabout putting people out.
我炒人鱿鱼已经炒腻烦了
With all due respect,nina,won't be an issue.
我明白你的意思 Nina 但我不会那样的
I can leave home at home.
家里的事我不会带到工作
And it's not gonna breakyour heart to leave thosesad little faces behind?
你会舍得那一张张伤心的小脸么
are you kidding?
你开玩笑吧？
This office is paradise--
这里是天堂 成年人谈成年人的事
grown-ups talking aboutgrown-up things.
No screaming,no vomiting,no boogers under the table.
没有叫嚷 没有呕吐 桌子下面也没有鼻屎
You're gonna have todrag me outta here kicking and screaming--
你拽我出去我也哭着喊着不会走
weekends,holidays,whenever.
周末 假期 随时待命
All right,ed wants to makethe final decision.
好吧 Ed要做最终决定
So I willbring you back tomorrow at 3 for a follow-up.
明天下午3点你再来
Well,that--that sounds great. Thank you--
好 那好极了 谢谢
lynette,be early.Show me something.
Lynette 早点到 证明给我看
Okay.
好
No way.Dad did not have a teddy bear.
不可能 爸爸不会有泰迪熊的
He most certainly did.
他当然有 他叫Doolittle
Oh,that was doolittle.
Your father never wentanywhere without him.
你爸爸走到哪都带着它
Here's your tea,phyllis.
你的茶 Phyllis
Oh.
哦 看 Bree
Look,bree.
This was the tiethat rex wore when he graduatedfrom prep school.
这是Rex在预备学校毕业时带的领带
I think he should wear it.
我想他应该带这条 我是说葬礼时候
You know,for the funeral?
Phyllis,that's an orange tie.
Phyllis 这是桔黄色的
Well,those werehis school colors--green and orange.
这是他学校的代表色 绿和橙
Well,um,he's being buriedin a blue suit.
他当天要穿一套蓝色西装下葬
maybe he could be buriedin a different suit.
或者他可以穿别的颜色的衣服
I don't think so,but thank you,though.
还是不要了吧 但是谢谢你了
You,uh,you keptdad's old comic books?
你留着爸爸的漫画书？
Oh,yes,I kept everything.
哦 是啊 我什么都没扔
Look here.
看 我连他床垫下面藏的色情杂志都留着呢
I even keptthe dirty magazine that he hidunder his mattress.
He didn't thinkI knew about it,but I did.
他还以为我不知道 我可了如指掌
well,looks like dadwas into big breasts.
看来爸爸喜欢大胸脯的
Oh,yes.
对阿 所以当他娶你妈的时候我吃惊够呛
That's why I was surprisedwhen he married your mother.
So you're just not gonnatalk to me,is that it?
你就打算不跟我说话了是么
Fine.
行啊 那我也不说了
I don't need to talk.
Okay. Yes,I hada little affair.
行了 对！ 我是偷了点情
It wasn't the best thing to do,and I'm not proud of it.
这不是什么好事 我也脸上无光
But it's not the worst thingthat could have happened.
但这也没什么大不了的啊
Nobody died.
谁也没死了阿
Oh,don't be such a martyr,carlos.
哦 别跟个烈士似的 Carlos
Okay,it takes two people.
一个巴掌拍不响
How many times did you go offon your little business trips
你没完没了的出差把我一个人丢在家里
and leave me alone?
See,so technically,you cheated,too.
所以也可以说你也偷情了
It's just your mistresswas your work.
只不过你的小情人是工作
No,okay.That was a stretch.I'm sorry.
别走 好吧 我有点瞎扯了 对不起
Carlos,wait! Come back.Look,I wanna start over.
carlos 别走 回来 我想从头来过
We're gonna have a baby.
我们就要有孩子了
Isn't thatwhat you always wanted?
你不是一直想要当爸爸么
Carlos,wait!
Carlos 等等 我说了对不起了 我爱你
I said I was sorryand I love you!
What more do you want?!
你还想要我怎么样
I want a paternity test.
我想要你做亲子鉴定
Mrs. Applewhite,hi.
Applewhite太太 你好
I am bree van de kamp,
我是bree van de kamp
and this ismy daughter danielle.
这是我女儿Danielle
- Hello.
- 你好
hi.
嗨
Hey,I'm matthew.This is my son.
嗨 我是Matthew 这是我儿子
Hi. I would have been oversooner to introduce myself,
我本该早点来拜访的
but I'm afraid there's beena death in my family.
但最近家中不幸有人过时
My dad.
我爸爸
I'm so sorry.I lost my dad,too.
我真遗憾
I know what you must begoing through right now.
我爸爸也过世了 我明白你现在的感受
Thank you.
谢谢
Anyway,I'm afraidthat my visit has an ulterior motive.
总之 很抱歉恐怕我的来访是有些私人的目的的
The organist at our churchis on vacation,
我们教堂的风琴师度假去了
and edie britt mentioned that you used to bea concert pianist,and--
Edie Britt说你曾经是为钢琴师
I would be honoredto play for you.
我将很荣幸为您演奏
Why don't I bringsome sheet music over later
不如过一会我拿些乐谱去 我们可以选择以下曲子
and we can plansome selections?
Thank you. That's just a hugeweight off my shoulders.
谢谢你了 我松了口气了
Oh,these are for you.
- 哦 这是给你们的
How sweet.
你真客气
Bree,we widowshave to stick together.
Bree 丧夫的女人该互相帮忙的
Bye.
再见
Pretendingyour father's dead?
假装你父亲过世了？ 不觉得有点假么
Don't you find thata little morbid?
我只是觉得这样能帮我们圆谎 这不好么
Well,I just thought it couldhelp our cover story,okay?
我只是想 跟她们套套近乎
Just,you know,win 'em over.
Oh,sweetie.I know you meant well.
宝贝儿 我知道你是好意
But in the future,you leavethe cleverness to me.
但以后 小聪明还是留给我耍吧
Since when are we protectedby dorset security?
我们什么时候装德塞保安系统了
Oh,we're not.It's a deterrentin case zach comes back.
没有 就是用来吓唬Zach的 以防他回来
I told mikeI didn't sleep last night,so he got me this sign.
我跟Mike说我昨晚没睡 他就给我拿来了这个
That guy is so supportive.
他真周到
You know he's out right nowin a ride-along with the police searching for zach?
他现在开着车跟警察到处找Zach呢
- Really?
- 是么
Yeah.
对
He's determined to seethat kid behind bars.
他一心要把那小子送进监狱
So tomorrow at school I want you to leteverybody know
明天在学校 你要让每个人都知道
that we got this new,expensive security system.
咱们安了这个新的昂贵的保安系统
- Mom,just--
- 妈
work itinto the conversation.
想办法在谈话中提到
- You know,put the word out there
- 让他们都知道
I've gotta tell you something.
我想告诉你件事
- Emphasize the motion detectors.
- 强调我们有移动侦测器
Mom,stop,stop.Listen.
妈 停 停 听我说
What? What is it?
什么 怎么了
Yesterday I overheardmike telling that cop
昨天我听到Mike告诉警察 他不想控告Zach
that he didn't wannapress charges against zach.
He made the whole thingsound like it was your fault.
他把事情说得好像都是你的错一样
My fault?
我的错？
Hi. Uh,I needa paternity test.
你好 我需要一份亲子鉴定
Well,we'll just schedule youfor an exam.
好 那我们为你安排一次检查
Oh,no,no. I-I don't needto take a test.
哦 不用 不用 我不需要做检查
I am just tryingto reassure my husband of what I knowis true in my heart.
我很确定 我只是想安慰我的丈夫一下
So if you could just slip mesomeone else's test results,
所以你要能给我顺一份别人的检查结果
I could make my own.
我可以自己做一份
I got photoshopfor christmas.
圣诞节我得了photoshop做礼物
Oh,come on.
哦 行了 你看来挺能疯的
You look likea fun-loving girl.
I am sure you've been in a couple hairy situationsof your own.
我想你肯定也有过几次特别状况了
Just because I chooseto express myself
我喜欢表现自己 并不意味着我会去跟人通奸
doesn't mean thatI condone adultery.
Sorry.
抱歉
Paternity test results?
亲子鉴定结果么？
I know.I'm in the same situation.
我明白 我也跟你一样
- Really? - Mm-hmm.
真的么
I just found outthe clinic screwed up
我刚发现我的医生搞错了
and gave me an eggthat belonged to some lesbian.
把一个女同性恋的卵子给了我
It was supposed to beimplanted in her lover,
本来该移入她爱人体内的
and nowmy husband's freaking out
现在我丈夫慌了
because he thinks thatour baby's gonna be gay!
他认为我们的孩子会是同性恋
Okay. We're inslightly different situations.
那我们的情况看来不太相同
But do you wanna geta cup of coffee and talk about it?
但你愿意一起喝杯咖啡谈谈这件事么
Yeah. That'd be nice.Thanks.
嗯 可以阿 谢谢
Yeah. Us girlshave to stick together.
嗯 女人应该互相帮助的
We shouldn't letthat stupid piece of paper ruin our life.
不能让一张破纸毁了我们的生活
Yeah!
说得对
Obviously,I've known rex for years,
很显然我认识Rex好多年了
but when it comesto writing a eulogy,
但要我写赞辞 我还是希望多听听家人的意见
I like as much inputfrom the family as possible.
Oh. Well,um,what kind of input?
哦 那要什么样的意见呢
Oh,well,he means anecdotes,
他是指一些佳话 小故事
little stories.
Isn't that what you mean,reverend?
您是这个意思吧 牧师
Well,yes,but,uh,also--
嗯 是啊 但也需要...
I thought thatyou might need some help,
我就知道你会需要点帮助
so last nightI stayed up all night
所以昨晚我一夜没睡
and tried to rememberfunny things
回想一些有趣的事情和时刻
and moments that said so muchabout rex as a person.
能让人感受到Rex的为人
My. How--how many pagesdo you have there?
天哪你写了多少页阿
15.
15页
well,you're hardlygoing to have to write anything at all,reverend.
您没有必要再多写什么了 牧师
Some of those anecdotesare just priceless.
那里有些逸事是无价的
Phyllis,these are all thingsthat happened to rex before he went to college.
Phyllis 这些都是Rex上大学以前的事情啊
So?
那怎么了
Well,don't you think it'd benice if reverend devoted
你不觉得让牧师在赞辞中 多涉及他婚后的生活更好些么
part of the eulogy to his lifeafter he was married?
Oh,well,yes,of course.
哦 是啊 当然了
The reverend will mentionthat part of his life.
牧师当然会提到那部分的
He's going to do morethan mention it.
光提到是不够的
That's the parthe'll focus on.
那将是他最主要的部分
In fact,I think three anecdotesfrom rex's childhood is more than enough.
事实上 我想3个Rex童年的逸事已经足矣了
Um,that--that seems fair.
看来满公平的
Well,whatever you thinkis appropriate.
您觉得合适就好
Fine.
很好
I just thoughtif we were going to focus on a time in rex's life,
我只是觉得既然我们要 着重讲他生命中的某一段时期
that we might as well focuson the happiest time.
何不选择他生活中最快乐的时光呢
let's talk flowers.
我们选选当天的花吧
Now I knowlilies are traditional,
我知道百合比较传统
but I think I can get youa deal on some white roses.
但我想我能帮你们订到一些白玫瑰
Reverend,if you don't call her on that incrediblyinsensitive comment,
牧师 您要是不对她刚才过分伤人的评论说点什么的话
I'm gonna lose it.
我就要发火了
I'm sure she didn't mean itthe way it sounded.
我想她不是那个意思
- I knew exactlywhat I was saying.
- 我很清楚我说的话
Ladies--
女士们
the happiest timein rex's life was not his childhood.
rex最幸福的时光不是他的童年
He loved being a husband,and he loved being a father.
他享受为人之夫 也享受为人之父
Well,he may have lovedbeing a father,
是 他可能确实是一个幸福的父亲
but your marriagewas a disaster.
但你们的婚姻一塌糊涂
Phyllis,is there somethingyou'd like to say?
Phyllis,你有话就直说吧
You made the last yearsof rex's life miserable,
你让Rex生前的最后时光苦不堪言
and now he's dead,
现在他死了
and he'll never haveanother chance at happiness.
他再也没有机会得到幸福了
You are no longerinvited to the funeral.
你不再受邀参加葬礼了
What?
什么
- You're not serious.
- 你不是认真的吧
Oh,yes,I am.
是的 我很认真
I am going to hire security,
我会雇用保安
and those security menare going to have sticks,
保安人员手里拿着棍子
and if you so much asset foot in that sanctuary,
你要是敢走近教堂半步
they will be instructedto beat you with those sticks.
他们就会听命用棍子打你.
Bree,this is your grief talking--
Bree,这只是你一时悲痛的气话
reverend,if you don'tback me up on this,so help me,
牧师,你要是不站在我这边,我发誓
I will pull the funeral out of your church.
我就不在你的教堂举办葬礼
- Bree!
I am not kidding.
我没开玩笑
I will go nondenominationalso fast,it will make your head spin.
我会马上脱离宗教 快的让你脑袋打转
Susan,I heardwhat happened with zach.
Susan,我听说zach的事了
How are you doing?
你还好吧?
- Fine. Is mike here?
- 挺好的 mike在么?
Inside.
在屋里
Jeez. You must have beenterrified.
天啊. 你一定是吓坏了
I mean,he put poor feliciain the hospital.
我是说 他把felica伤的住进医院了
- Did he pistol-whip you?
- 他用手枪抡你了么
No.
没有
Oh,come on.You can tell me.
噢 行了 跟我说说
- Did he slap you around?
- 他扇你耳光了么
No.
没有.
Well,don't get me wrong.I'm thrilled that you're okay.
别误会我 我很高兴你平安无事
It's just that when someoneholds someone else hostage,
只是一般有人绑架别人的时候
they usuallyrough 'em up a little.
他们总会施点暴力
It wasn't like that.
当时不是那样的
- Not even a little kicking?
- 甚至都没踢你几下么
Edie...
someone to see you.
有人找你
- Well,hey,how's it goin'?
- 嗨 还好吧？
Good.
很好
So there'sa rumor going around
我听到些传闻
that you don't wannapress charges against zach.
说你不会控告Zach
Is that true?
是真的么
Yeah.
对
Wow. Um... I find that...confusing.
哦  我有点...不太明白
Look,if we makea big deal out of this,
听我说 要是咱们把这件事搞大
he could end upgoing to prison.
他会进监狱的
He held a gun to my face,so I'm thinking,"good."
他拿枪指着我的脸来着 所以我想 他进监狱倒不错
I've been to prison.He couldn't handle it.
我蹲过监狱 他受不了的
- Who cares?
- 谁在乎呢？
I care.
我在乎
Well,you should caremore about me.
你应该更在乎我
I'm your girlfriend.We're moving in together.
我是你女朋友 我们就要一起生活了
He's just a neighbor.You don't even know zach.
他只是个邻居 你都不了解他
I know enough about him to knowthat deep down,he's a good kid.
据我所知我足以知道 他本性不坏的
Mike,he wanted to kill you.
Mike 他想杀了你
But he didn'T.
但他没有
You never asked me whyzach wanted to shoot you.
你从来没问我zach为什么要杀你
Aren't you curious?Does it matter?
你不好奇么? 这有关系么？
Zach said you kidnappedhis father so you could kill him.
Zach说你绑架了他爸爸 说你要杀了他
I didn't kill paul young.
我没杀paul young
I didn't think you did.Now tell me why zach does.
我知道你没有 但告诉我为什么zach以为你做了
I found some evidencethat suggested that paul murdered deirdre.
我找到些证据 证明paul杀了deirdre
16 years agodeirdre had a baby,
16年前deirdre生了个孩子
and paul and mary alice youngkidnapped him
paul和mary alice young拐走了孩子
and raised him as their own.
把他当作自己的来养
Deirdre tracked him down hereto wisteria lane and demanded her baby back.
Deirdre来到wisteria lane 找到了他 想要回她的孩子
So paul killed her?
然后Paul就杀了她？
Actually,it was mary alice.
事实上 是mary alice
Oh,my god.
哦 天哪
Mike?
I answered your phone.
我接了你的电话
It's the police.
是警察
Yeah. Delfino.
我是Delfino
You did?
真的么？
Okay,I can be therein 20 minutes.
好 我20分钟以后到
Zach's dead.
Zach死了
They want me to comeidentify the body.
他们让我去辨认尸体
Thanks for coming down.
感谢你们来
Since the kid's fatheris missing,
他的爸爸失踪了
we didn't knowwho else to call.
我们不知道该找谁来
So... you folks ready?
你们准备好了么
that's not zach.
这不是zach.
You're sure?
你确定么
He had a gun in my facefor six hours.
他拿枪对着我足足6个小时
I know what he looks like.
我知道他长什么样
- Can you give us a minute?
- 我们能私下说几句话么
Sure.
当然
- Zach is your son,isn't he?
- Zach是你的儿子 是不是？
Yeah.
对
I'm pretty sure.
我很确定
How long have you known?
你知道多久了
Paul young told me.
Paul young 告诉我的
Deirdre got pregnantbefore I went to jail
Deirdre在我进监狱以前怀孕了
and,um,told meshe had an abortion.
后来她说她流产了
Guess she lied.
估计她骗了我
I see.
我明白了
When I took paulout to the desert,
当我带paul去沙漠的时候
and I was so angry,I just wanted to hurt him...
我很愤怒 我一心让他吃点苦头
the way they hurt deirdre.
像他们对deirdre做的那样.
But then when he told me
但然后他告诉我
that he and mary alice hadtaken care of deirdre's baby--
他和mary alice在抚养deirdre的孩子
my baby...
我的孩子
that rage just went away.
我的愤怒一下子消失了
Kept me from doingsomething really stupid.
没有了想做蠢事的念头
I'm gonna take a cab home,okay?
我先打车回家了 好么？
Mom,grandma's leaving,all right?You have to talk to her.
妈 奶奶要走了 知道么 你得跟她谈谈
No,I don'T. If you heardthe things that she said to me--
我不谈 你要是听到了她当时对我说的话
look,I'm sure she wasa real bitch,okay?
我知道她对你很无情
But she's family,so that makes her our bitch.
但她是家里人 我们得受着
Let her say good-byeto dad.
让她跟爸爸道别
She went out of her wayto be cruel to me.
她对我残酷得太过分了
I don't want her at the funeral.
我不想在葬礼看到她
Mom,if you don't let grandmacome,I will never forgive you.
妈 你要是不让奶奶参加葬礼 我永远也不原谅你
Did I ask for your help?
我用你帮忙了么？
You know dadwould want her there.
你很清楚爸爸希望奶奶在的
It's true rex and I did nothave the perfect marriage,
rex和我的婚姻确实不算美满
but for 18 yearsI tried my very best,
但18年来我已经倾尽了我的全部
and for that I am entitledto your respect.
为这 你应该尊重我
Of course you are.
你当然努力了
Of course I respect you.
而且我也尊重你
Well,then why did you saythose things to me?
那你为什么对我说那些话
I guess I thought it would beeasier to be angry at you
我只是觉得对你发脾气更容易一些
than to be angry with rex.
我已经不能对rex发脾气了
I mean,what was he thinking,
我是说 他怎么能这样
leaving me?
就这么离开了？
I do want you to cometo the funeral.
我想让你来参加葬礼
you don't know whatthat means to me,bree.
这对我来说太重要了 bree
Thank you.
谢谢你
Someone should get my luggage.
找个人帮我搬行李
Okay,let's get outta here.Tom?
好了 咱们到客厅来 Tom?
- yeah? - Mom.
干嘛
What's the matter?
你怎么了
My back--I threw it out. I washolding parker upside down.
我的后背 我抻着了 我刚才拎着parker玩倒立
Okay. Come on.Give me your feet.
好吧 来 抬脚
how's that?Is that better?
怎么样 好点了么
honey,can you push the interview?
亲爱的 你能推迟面试么
Because I don't thinkI'm gonna be able
我想我这样没法带penny了
to take care of penny like this.
Don't do this to me.
别跟我来这套
I don't have timeto make a phone call,
我没时间打电话
and I promised that womanI would not let the kids
而且我跟那女的保证了 我不会因为孩子影响工作
interfere with this job.
But that wasa stupid promise.
但这个保证够蠢的
Remember that time whenyou were away in tucson,and I had a 104 fever,
还记得那年你在土孙（城市）出差 我发了高烧
but I still managed to take the kids trick-or-treating?
但还是坚持下来带孩子过万圣节
honey...
亲爱的
I don't think that's helping.
这样没用
Tom,being a mom is likebeing an E.R. Doctor.
Tom 当母亲就像当急诊室医生
There are no days off,so get up! Get up!
没有休息日 给我起来 起来
Okay.
好
Jeez,are you crying?
天哪 你在哭么
Just a little.
算是吧
I'll be fine. You just... go.Just go.
我没事 你走吧 快走吧
oh,for god sakes.
哦 真要了命了
Give 'em hell,honey.
给他们点颜色看看 宝贝儿
You...
你
hi,mrs. Scavo.You can wait inside.
嗨Scavo太太 你可以进去等
- They'll be right in.
- 他们马上就到
Great.
很好
Listen,uh...
听我说 唔。。
- stu.
- 我叫Stu
Stu.
Stu
You look like a bright,uh,responsible young man,
你看起来应该是一个聪明 有责任心的年轻人
and I bet you just love kids.Am I right?
你肯定很爱小孩子吧 我说得对吧
Ed ferrara,lynette scavo.
这是Ed ferrara 这是lynette scavo.
Thanks so muchfor having me in.
谢谢您给我这个机会
Nice to meet you.Please,sit.
很高兴见到你 请坐
Thank you.
谢谢
We're gonna have tomake this quick.
咱们得快点进行
I gotta leave in fiveto catch a plane.
我五点需要赶一趟飞机
I got celtic ticketson the floor.
我拿到celtic的场地票了
This is a great r閟um?
简历不错
I see you workedwith the donahues.
你在donahues工作过
You know,I snakedthe oslo candy account from 'em last year.
知道么 去年我在oslo糖果的帐目上狠杀了他们一回
So you've donea lot of copy work?
你作过很多文案工作？
I have. But when I movedover to cenn and simmons,
是的 但当我到cenn and simmons工作以后
um,I got to doa broader range of campaigns.
我的工作范围拓宽了不少
T...
电...
uh,V...
视...
and... uh...
还有...阿..
radio...
广播...
uh,billboards.
公告牌
could you excuse mefor a minute?
原谅我失陪一下
Please?
不好意思
What's going on?
怎么回事
I have no idea.
搞不清楚
Stu,you are an idiot.
Stu 你是个白痴
You're an idiot,an absolute idiot.
你真白痴 纯粹的白痴
Hi.
嗨
Ha! Guys,I'd like youto meet penny.
哈 大家 我想让你们见见penny
She gives meall my best ideas.
她是我灵感的源泉
You brought your babyto the interview.
你把孩子带来面试？
- It won't be an ongoing thing.
- 我发誓就这一次
You bet it won'T.
当然就只会是这一次
Nina,it's fine.
Nina 没关系的
Any chance we can getthat little lady to be quiet?
但你能让这位小女士安静下来么
Not until I change her diaper.
只要我换了尿布就行
Could you just give metwo minutes?
能给我两分钟么
Sorry. Plane.Well...
对不起 我要赶飞机
then watch me multitask.
那... 我就一心多用吧
Here's how I see it.
我是这么想的
You guys runa really good shop,
你们的公司干得不错
but if you want your agencyto go to the next level,
但你们要是想更上一层楼
you have to focuson two things.
有两件事你们要重点考虑
First,you've gotta winsome awards.
首先 你们得赢些大奖
Do some P.S.A.S,pro bono stuff,whatever it takes,
作些P.S.A.S 公益服务之类的 该做什么就要做
because whetherthey admit it or not,
因为不管客户承不承认
clients care aboutwhat's in your trophy case.
他们非常在乎你们的奖杯陈列柜
Two--your web site.
第二 网站
It's the first thinga client's gonna look at,
它是客户第一眼看到的东西
and it's hard to navigate.There's no site map.
你们的网站太难操作了 还没有网站地图
It just wasn't builtfor people who grow up without computers.
电脑知识不强的人根本没法浏览你们的网站
There. And third...
第三
I don't have a third.
没有第三了
Yeah,so that'S... it.
好了 我就要说这些
Okay.
好吧
You're in.
你被录用了
- Seriously?
- 真的么
Yeah.
对
Take the office across the hall.I gotta run.
门厅对面是你的办公室 我得走了
Well,all right!
哦 好极了
Okay,obviously,I'm gonna clean that up.
好吧 真的 我会把它收拾干净的
Here it is in black and white.It's your kid.
白纸黑字你看好了 是你的孩子
What?Why aren't you smiling?
怎么了 怎么不笑笑
It's not enough.
还不够
What do you want,a father's day card?
你想要什么 父亲节卡片？
You knew the one thingthat I demanded was fidelity,
你明知道对我最最重要的就是忠诚
and you still went outand screwed around behind my back.
你还是在我背后和人鬼混
You knew the one thingI didn't want was a child,
你明知道我最最不想要的就是孩子
and you still tricked me into getting pregnant.
你还是设下陷阱让我怀了孕
It's not the same thing.
不是一回事
Damn straight.What you did was worse.
真他妈说对了 你做得更过分
We're not very nice people,are we?
我们不是什么善男信女 不是么
No,we're not.
我们不是
Oh,when we got married,
哦 我们结婚的时候
I thought we were gonna beso happy.
我以为我们会很幸福
Me too.
我也是
Look on the bright side.At least we're still rich.
往好的方面看 我们还是富人
Thank god for that.
感谢上帝
So it occurred to me...
我后来想到
that I was really rudeat the morgue.
我在停尸房时候有点粗鲁了
When you told me about zach,I was so busy freaking out,
当你告诉我zach是你儿子的时候 我只顾着惊慌
I never actuallycongratulated you.
却忘了祝贺你
Congratulated me?
祝贺我？
Yeah,I know how muchyou've always wanted a child,
是啊我知道你一直多么希望有个孩子
and now you have one.
你现在有了
Thanks.
谢谢
Obviously,um,it was quite a shock,
很显然 我很震惊
but it's good newsany way you slice it.
但不论怎么看这是个好消息
What's wrong?
你怎么了
So naturally you'll bewanting to...
很自然你想
have a relationship with him,and that takes time,
和他发展好父子关系 而那需要时间
- a lot of time.
- 很多时间
Susan--
susan
and out of all the mixed-upteenagers in the world,
而在这世界上所有的问题青年中
zach is just the one kidthat I can't be around.
zach是最让我没法相处的孩子
I can't have juliearound him.
我不能让他靠近julie
So,um,what I'm tryingto say is...
所以 我想说的就是
we can't move in together.
我们不能一起生活了
But I am so happy for you.
但我为你高兴
Really,you have a child,and that is good for you.
真的 你有个儿子 这是件好事
Isn't there any way--
难道就不能..
no. No,I...
不 不能
so sorry.
对不起
I'll--I'll,um,
我..
I'll see you around.
再见了
today we've come togetherto celebrate the life
今天我们聚集于此
of dr. Rex van de kamp...
来赞颂Van de Camp医生走过的人生
what is he wearing?
他带的是什么
What?
什么
I left him an hour ago,
一个小时前我离开他的时候
and he was wearingralph lauren.
他的领带是ralph lauren（时装品牌）
But it's what rexwould have wanted.
但这条是Rex想要的
He loved that prep school.
他爱他的预备学校生活
...But whichever coathe was wearing,
但无论他身着什么
rex always broughtan irresistible enthusiasm
Rex总是以难以抗拒的热情
and a single-mindeddetermination to...
不二的决心...
so as we mourn the passingof rex van de kamp,
在我们为rex van de kamp哀悼的同时
we give thanks to god,
我们感谢上帝
for we do not grieveas those who have no hope
感谢我们的悲痛不似那些无望的灵魂
but as those who placetheir trust in god.
感谢 因我们心奉上帝
wait!
等等！
do not closethat coffin.
不要盖上棺木
Give me your tie.
把你的领带给我
What?
什么
Give me your tie.
给我领带
give it to her!Give it to her.
给她 快给她
You look magnificent.
你看起来高尚极了
so it looks like mary alicekilled zach's birth mother
事情好像就是这样 mary alice为了不让zach被带走
in order to keep herfrom taking zach away.
杀了他的生母
Oh,my god.
天哪
I mean,I knew mary alicehad killed herself
我是说 我知道mary alice一定是 因为一件很严重的事而自杀 但没想到
over something big,but wow.
Can you imagine livingwith that guilt?
你能想像如何带着那种罪恶感生活么
Isn't it bizarrethat paul and mary alice
这不是很奇异么 paul和mary alice这些年来
had this secretall those years,
一直带着这个秘密生活
and we didn't evenknow about it?
我们竟一点没有察觉
No,not really.
不 我不觉得
I mean,what do we actuallyknow about our neighbors?
我是说 我们到底了解我们的邻居多少
I mean,we can tellif they keep their lawns nice
我们能看到他们的草坪修剪得很好
or they taketheir trash cans in,
能知道他们把垃圾桶拿进房子
but when they do those things,we stop asking questions
但只要他们做这些事 我们就不再多问了
'cause if people aregood neighbors...
因为只要他们是个好邻居
we don't really carewhat happens behind closed doors.
我们就不会去在乎门后面发生着什么
It had been one year since my suicide...
（我自杀后已经过去一年了）
makes you wonder,doesn't it?
值得思索阿 不是么
And a lot had changed on wisteria lane.
（Wisteria Lane上发生了很多改变）
There were new flowers,
(新的花儿)
new houses
(新的房子)
and new neighbors--
(还有 新的邻居)
the kind anyone would want living right next door.
(人人心中理想的那种好邻居) (住进了隔壁)
is that another hymn?
另一首赞美诗吗?
I know. It's silly,
我知道 有点荒谬吧
but playing those songstoday at the funeral
但在葬礼弹得那些曲子让我来了情绪
just got me in the mood.
This isyour grandmother's favorite.
这首是你外婆最喜欢的
Did you remember butter?
你没忘了黄油吧
I make up this trayevery night.
每晚托盘都是我弄得
Of course you do.I'm sorry.
可不是吗 对不起
Oh,look.
哦 看啊
You added a flower.
你放了朵花
Thought it'd be nice.
觉得这样会不错
How'd I get so luckyto have a child like you?
我怎么这么幸运有你这么个儿子
You really do try to thinkabout us.
你总是想着我们
That flower isa small act of kindness
那朵花是善心的小小表现
you thoughtno one would notice,
你以为没人会留意
and yet you did it anyway.
但你还是这么做了
Says a lot abouthow you were raised.
说明教子有方
Well,I guessyou did your job.
是啊 亏了你这称职的母亲
Thank yourself.
感谢你自己吧
I'll get the tray.
我来端托盘
You take the gun.
你拿枪
It really is a lovely gesture.
你真善良
Sync:YTET-fisherchen -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 七宝 校对: 七宝 时间轴: fisherchen